Finding aid to the Mary Daly papers SSC.MS.00637
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES III. Correspondence, 1960-2013; 10.833 linear feet (14 containers)
  - Kathy Barry (Box 47)
  - Regina Barshak (Box 47)
  - Jane Caputi (Box 47)
  - Peggy Chinn (Box 47)
  - Carol Christ, Phyllis Chesler (Box 47)
  - A. Collard (Box 47)
  - Emily Culpepper (Box 47)
  - Elizabeth Farians (Box 47)
  - Elizabeth Gould Davis (Box 47)
  - Melissa Fletcher (Box 47)
  - Marilyn Frye (Box 47)
  - Tine Govaart-Halkes (Box 47)
  - Helen & John Gray (Box 47)
  - Pat Green (Box 47)
  - Gloria Greenfield (Box 47)
  - Susan Griffin (Box 47)
  - Feminist press (Box 47)
  - Feminist resources (Box 47)
  - Feminist Spirituality Center (Box 47)
  - Feminist Writers' Guild (Box 47)
  - Firings-Christiane Joost (Box 47)
  - Firings-Misc (Box 47)
  - International Tribunal on Crimes Against Women (Box 48)
  - International Women's Year (Box 48)
  - Jobs Available for Women (Box 48)
  - Joint Committee (Box 48)
  - Know, Inc. (Box 48)
  - Management (Box 48)
  - National Women's Political Caucus (Box 48)
  - New Alexandria Lesbian Library (Box 48)
  - New Haven Feminist Union (Box 48)
  - Newsletters-AAR Women's Caucus (Box 48)
  - Newsletters-Australian National Advisory Committee (Box 48)
  - Newsletters-American Council on Education (Box 48)
  - Newsletters-Cambridge Women's Center (Box 48)
  - Newsletters-CIDAL (Box 48)
  - Newsletters-Department of Labor Women's Bureau (Box 48)
  - Newsletters-Radical Philosophers' News Journal (Box 48)
  - Newsletters-Vietnam Women's Union (Box 48)
  - Newsletters-WEAL (Box 48)
  - Women Against Violence in Pornography & Media (Box 48)
  - Pergamon Press, Oxford (Box 48)
  - New Words Bookstore (Box 48)
  - Women's Studies Newsletter (Box 48)
  - Politics (Box 48)
  - Quest Quarterly (Box 48)
  - Religious Coalition for Abortion Rights (Box 48)
  - Requests for jobs-vitas (Box 48)
  - Self Help Women's Community Health Center (Box 48)
  - Schlesinger Library (Box 48)
  - Sinister Wisdom (Box 48)
  - Feminist songs (Box 48)
  - Spinsters, Ink. (Box 48)
  - Three Marias (Box 48)
  - Womancraft (Box 48)
  - Women's Counseling & Resource Center (Box 48)
  - WEAL (Box 48)
  - Wellesley Center for Research on Women (Box 48)
  - Wicca (Box 48)
  - The Women's Building, L.A. (Box 48)
  - Women's Center (Box 48)
  - Women's Community Health Center (Box 48)
  - Women's Community Planning Conference (Box 48)
  - Women's Country House (Box 48)
  - Women's Studies Bibliography (Box 48)
  - Women's Studies Guide to Female Studies (Box 48)
  - Women's Studies International Quarterly (Box 48)
  - Women's Studies programs (Box 48)
  - Women's Studies rape (Box 48)
  - Women's Studies vasectomy (Box 48)
  - WONAAC (Box 48)
  - Elise Young (Box 48)
  - Your Place & Mine (Box 48)
  - Newsletters-Diaspora (Box 48)
  - Newsletters-Genesis III (Box 48)
  - Newsletters-Graduate Theological Union Office of Women's Affairs (Box 48)
  - Newsletters-In Our Own Write (Box 48)
  - Newsletters-Institute for Policy Studies (Box 48)
  - Newsletters-The Journey (Box 48)
  - Newsletters-Know, Inc. (Box 48)
  - Newsletters-Link (Box 48)
  - Newsletters- Media Report to Women (Box 48)
  - NOW (Box 48)
  - National Women's Political Caucus (Box 48)
  - St. Joan's Alliance The Catholic Citizen (Box 48)
  - Sue Bellamy and Janet Runsen [sp?] (Box 48)
  - Letters from Australia, 1981 (Box 48)
  - Lesbian Perspectives for Women's Studies (Box 48)
  - Barry MacMaster (Box 48)
  - Pat Harrison (II) (Box 48)
  - Pat Styer (Box 48)
  - Kate Millett (Box 48)
  - Diana Davies (Box 48)
  - Catherine Madsen, 2000 (Box 48)
  - Gretchen Van Ness (Box 48)
  - Aille Og - paychecks (Box 48)
  - Debra Campbell (Box 49)
  - Carl S. Derwig (Box 49)
  - Michel Dion (Box 49)
  - Dworkin-Scapegoat (Box 49)
  - Lori Getz-letter UNC, October 27, 1999 (Box 49)
  - Lori Getz (Box 49)
  - Doris Gunn (Box 49)
  - Esther Heggie "Fire" (Box 49)
  - Barbara Hope (Box 49)
  - Mary Hunt (Box 49)
  - Linda McCord (Box 49)
  - Vicki Noble (Box 49)
  - Ann Marie Palmisciano (Box 49)
  - French manuscript (Box 49)
  - Suzanne Bellamy (Box 49)
  - Phyllis Chesler (Box 49)
  - Copyright Clearance Center (Box 49)
  - Jodi Solomon (Box 49)
  - Carol Adams and Gale Research (Box 49)
  - Cow (Box 49)
  - June Campbell- good review for The Women's Review of Books (Box 49)
  - College of Saint Rose, honorary degree (Box 49)
  - Erin Snow (Box 49)
  - Sandie Woo (Box 49)
  - Gerda Kallup (Box 49)
  - Shannon Lowney (Box 49)
  - Sandy Madill (Box 49)
  - McGraw Hill Permissions Group (Box 49)
  - National Writers' Union (Box 49)
  - Elizabeth Farians (Box 49)
  - Hye Sook Hwang (Box 49)
  - Jan Goodwin (Box 49)
  - American Program Bureau (Box 49)
  - Abortion-Commonweal (Box 49)
  - Affirmative action (Box 49)
  - AAR (Box 49)
  - Agents-literary (Box 49)
  - Cuernavaca (Box 49)
  - Dance (Box 49)
  - Diana Press (Box 49)
  - Emmatroupe (Box 49)
  - Employment (Box 49)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (Box 49)
  - Feminist art (Box 49)
  - Feminist Book Mart (Box 49)
  - Feminist books (Box 49)
  - Feminist credit union (Box 49)
  - Feminist dictionaries (Box 49)
  - Feminist films (Box 49)
  - Feminist (and related) periodicals (Box 49)
  - Canada Speech, 1982 (Box 49)
  - AAR (and BC travel reimbursement for it), 1984-1985 (Box 49)
  - Speaking engagements refused, 1984-1985 (Box 49)
  - AAUW (Box 49)
  - "Who's Who" info (Box 49)
  - Rediffusion Video Leasing (Box 49)
  - Seagull water purifier (Box 49)
  - SCP newsletter (Box 49)
  - Jo Yancey (Box 49)
  - Refuse & Resist (Box 50)
  - Anna Larson (Box 50)
  - Lawrence Lader (Box 50)
  - Phyllis Langer (Box 50)
  - Gary MacEoin (Box 50)
  - Tatyana Mamonova (Box 50)
  - Bonnie Mann (Box 50)
  - Zulma Nelly Martinez (Box 50)
  - Mary Ellen McCarthy (Box 50)
  - Mary Meigs (Box 50)
  - Nina Menkes (Box 50)
  - Ger Moane (Box 50)
  - Lisbeth Mogensen (Box 50)
  - Siobhan Molloy (Box 50)
  - Honor Moore (Box 50)
  - Robin Morgan (Box 50)
  - Nelle Morton (Box 50)
  - Nelle Morton-The Journey is Home (Box 50)
  - Camille Norton (Box 50)
  - Barbara Pade-Theisen (Box 50)
  - Ann-Marie Palmisciano (Box 50)
  - Julia Penelope (Box 50)
  - Radioactivity (Box 50)
  - Sudie Rakusin (Box 50)
  - Sudie Rakusin-extra drawings (Box 50)
  - Charlotte Redmond (Box 50)
  - Jan Raymond blurb for Women as Wombs, 1993 (Box 50)
  - Marilyn Waring (Box 50)
  - Demaris Wehr (Box 50)
  - Judith Wilt (Box 50)
  - Erika Wisselinck and Ginster Votteler (Box 50)
  - Pergamon correspondence Sexual Liberals (Box 50)
  - Ann Marie Palmisciano (Box 50)
  - Linnea Pierson (Box 50)
  - Postmodernism articles (Box 50)
  - Erika Wisselinck (Box 50)
  - Monique Wittig (Box 50)
  - Martha Yates (Box 50)
  - Barbara Zanotti (Box 50)
  - Marisa Zavalloni (Box 50)
  - Janice Raymond (Box 50)
  - Janice Raymond [articles?] etc., 1970's (Box 50)
  - Janice Raymond-Handbook for Women Scholars-B.C. (Box 50)
  - Loose notes (Box 50)
  - Adrienne Rich (Box 50)
  - Jeremy Rifkin (Box 50)
  - Rise Riyo (Box 50)
  - Marge [?] (Box 50)
  - Alexandra Owen (Box 50)
  - Liz Seaborn (Box 50)
  - Archbishop Simonis (Box 50)
  - Johanna Sizich (Box 50)
  - Monica Sjoo (Box 50)
  - Jeff Smith (Box 50)
  - Dale Spender (Box 50)
  - Diane Stein (Box 50)
  - Barbara Starrett (Box 50)
  - Mary Stockton (Box 50)
  - Judith Anna Stofer (Fribourg) (Box 50)
  - Merlin Stone (Box 50)
  - Claire Tourigny (Box 50)
  - Charles Virga (Box 50)
  - ACCA (Box 50)
  - Carol Adams (Box 50)
  - Jeffery Allen (Box 50)
  - Bread & Roses (Box 50)
  - Kaye Ashe (Box 50)
  - Atlantis (Box 50)
  - Kathy Barry (Box 50)
  - Batya Bauman (Box 50)
  - Nicole Brossard (Box 50)
  - Nicole Brossard-Sherbrooke (Box 50)
  - Gail Bryan (Box 50)
  - Ginny Berson (Box 50)
  - Lee Bowie (Box 50)
  - June Campbell (Box 50)
  - Jane Caputi, Wickedary royalties, Beacon Press (Box 50)
  - Jane Caputi-Bear & Company (Box 51)
  - Jane Caputi letters of reference (Box 51)
  - Jane Caputi (Box 51)
  - Gossips, Gorgons, and Crones manuscript, copy edited version (Box 51)
  - Michele Causse (Box 51)
  - Phyllis Chesler, 1993 (Box 51)
  - Peggy Chinn (Box 51)
  - Krystyna Colburn (Box 51)
  - Andree Collard (Box 51)
  - Denise D. Connors (Box 51)
  - Sheelagh Conway (Box 51)
  - Gena Corea (Box 51)
  - Emily Culpepper-B.C. petition (Box 51)
  - Rosemary Curb (Box 51)
  - Joni Crone (Box 51)
  - Doris Curry (Box 51)
  - A.E. Dropper (Box 51)
  - Frank X. Daly, Library of Congress (Box 51)
  - Diana Davies information (Box 51)
  - Andrea Dworkin (Box 51)
  - Externsteine (Box 51)
  - FBI (Box 51)
  - Felder (Box 51)
  - Feminists for Animal Rights (Box 51)
  - Melissa Fletcher (Box 51)
  - Melissa Fletcher: "Cow" title and letters (Box 51)
  - Lilian Friedberg (Box 51)
  - Marilyn Frye (Box 51)
  - Lisa Foley (Box 51)
  - Loose journals and calendar (Box 51)
  - Cassandra (Box 51)
  - Gay Community News (Box 51)
  - Lori Getz (Box 51)
  - Genevieve Gherashey (Box 51)
  - Gilbert and Gubar, NY Times (Box 51)
  - Anne Louise Gilligan (Box 51)
  - Sally Glover (Box 51)
  - Joey Green (Africa) (Box 51)
  - Doris Gunn (Box 51)
  - Daphne Hampson (Box 51)
  - Harmonic convergence (Box 51)
  - Esther Heggie (Box 51)
  - Helen Prize for Women (Box 51)
  - Moya Henderson (Box 51)
  - Shere Hite (Box 51)
  - Pat Hynes (Box 51)
  - Indiana University Press (Box 51)
  - Peggy Holland (Box 51)
  - Jan Johnson (Box 51)
  - Nancy Kelly (Box 51)
  - Gerda Kallup (Box 51)
  - Fern Johnson (Box 51)
  - Sonia Johnson (Box 51)
  - K&S (Box 51)
  - NWSA materials (Box 51)
  - Permissions, Australia (Box 51)
  - Pioneer Ecology (Box 51)
  - Pornography (Box 51)
  - Willie Tyson (Box 51)
  - George Wald (Box 51)
  - Erika Wisselinck (Box 51)
  - Julia Stanley (Box 51)
  - Leigh Star (Box 51)
  - Krister Stendahl (Box 51)
  - Gloria Steinem (Box 51)
  - Judith Wilt (Box 51)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 52)
  - Janet James (Box 52)
  - Pat Jonas (Box 52)
  - Mary Klages (Box 52)
  - Germaine Lafeuille (Box 52)
  - Marsha Lieberman (Box 52)
  - Robin Linden (Box 52)
  - Fran McCullough (Box 52)
  - Judith McDaniel (Box 52)
  - Ellen Mandel (Box 52)
  - Deena Metzger (Box 52)
  - Helen Mitrovka (Box 52)
  - Ellen Morgan (Box 52)
  - Robin Morgan (Box 52)
  - Eleanor Mullaly (Box 52)
  - Louise Mullaly (Box 52)
  - Pauli Murray (Box 52)
  - Ann Marie Palmisciano (Box 52)
  - Julia Penelope (Box 52)
  - Adrienne Rich papers (Box 52)
  - Adrienne Rich-Of WomanBorn (Box 52)
  - Adrienne Rich poems (Box 52)
  - Adrienne Rich (Box 52)
  - Satire (Box 52)
  - Susan Sontag (Box 52)
  - Sports, Karen Murphy (Box 52)
  - Tillich (Box 52)
  - Universities (Box 52)
  - Work (Box 52)
  - Vegetarianism (Box 52)
  - Violence (Box 52)
  - Alice Walker (Box 52)
  - Virginia Woolf (Box 52)
  - Warner Modular Publications (Box 52)
  - Transsexualism (Box 52)
  - Simone Weil (Box 52)
  - Witchcraft (Box 52)
  - Wizard (of Oz) (Box 52)
  - Marisa Zavalloni (Box 53)
  - Marisa Zavalloni-Hyperidentities (Box 53)
  - Cards and miscellaneous (Box 53)
  - Friends' mail, 1993 (Box 53)
  - BC speech: colleague and student responses, Spring 1993 (Box 53)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 53)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 53)
  - Correspondence answered and unanswered, 1988-1989 (Box 53)
  - Mail, 1988 (Box 53)
  - "Sister Nagsters" (Box 53)
  - "Her Underground"-Undine (Box 53)
  - "Other Skins" (Box 53)
  - Nikki Craft website (Box 53)
  - Mary Hunt (Box 53)
  - Gage Foundation (Box 53)
  - Mamonova (Box 53)
  - Robin Morgan on separation of church and state, Ms. Magazine (Box 53)
  - Gary MacEoin (Box 53)
  - Tovis Page (Box 53)
  - World population (Box 53)
  - Elizabeth Wolfe-final settlement agreement with BC, October 31, 2001 (Box 53)
  - Elizabeth Wolfe, 2001 (Box 53)
  - Ghost (Box 53)
  - Bills-paid (Box 53)
  - Friends (Box 53)
  - Emily Culpepper (Box 53)
  - Letters (Box 53)
  - Camille Norton University of Pacific (Box 53)
  - Ger Moane (Box 53)
  - Mary Hannahan and Stewart (Box 53)
  - Debra Moss (Box 53)
  - Peter Norman (Box 53)
  - Meg Heisse and Willow LaMonte (Box 53)
  - Mary and Betty Ewens (Box 53)
  - Jerome Thailing (Box 53)
  - Marilyn Rinaldi (Box 53)
  - Linda McCord (Box 54)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 54)
  - Jeremy German (Box 54)
  - Julie Madsen (Box 54)
  - Mary Hunt (Box 54)
  - Irish Friends (Box 54)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence 2 (Box 54)
  - Charlotte Miller (Box 54)
  - Emily Mann (Box 54)
  - Gary MacEoin (Box 54)
  - Miscellaneous Goo-Goo (Box 54)
  - Soapbox, 2003-2004 (Box 54)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 2001 (Box 54)
  - June Campbell (Box 54)
  - Jane Caputi (Box 54)
  - Kay Cornish-Mann (Box 54)
  - Michel Dion (Box 54)
  - Cats, Evelyn Embry (Box 54)
  - Betty Farians (Box 54)
  - Lori Getz (Box 54)
  - Glasgow Women's Center/Library (Box 54)
  - Sarah Hoagland and Marilyn Frye (Box 54)
  - Mary Hunt (Box 54)
  - Hye Sook Hwang (Box 54)
  - Mihaela Mironi (Box 54)
  - Vicki Noble (Box 54)
  - Kate Millett (Box 54)
  - Health/wisdom (Box 54)
  - Anna Pohl (Box 54)
  - Sudie's drawings and correspondence (Box 54)
  - Rindones and stuff [?] (Box 54)
  - Naomi Weisstein (Box 54)
  - Erika Wisselinck- Anna (Box 54)
  - Marisa Zavalloni (Box 54)
  - Cards (Box 54)
  - Ann Marie Palmisciano (Box 54)
  - Steinem and donors (Box 54)
  - Erika Wisselinck (Box 54)
  - Elizabeth Wolfe (Box 54)
  - Alexis De Veaux fax, June 30, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Audre Lorde letter Alexis De Veaux (Box 54)
  - Reviews-De Veaux on Lorde (Box 54)
  - Lorde Chapter 3 (Box 54)
  - Audre Lorde chronology (Box 54)
  - Sandy Heimann (Box 54)
  - NWSA, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Ann Marie Palmisciano (Box 54)
  - Cindy Griffin (Box 54)
  - Sarah Roche-Mahdi (Box 54)
  - Betsy Beaven (Box 54)
  - Cynthia Eiler (Box 54)
  - Nikki Craft (Box 54)
  - Dworkin memorial (Box 54)
  - Pioneer Feminist Project, Barbara Love (Box 54)
  - The Feminist Majority (Box 54)
  - The Engager (Box 54)
  - Bloodroot (Box 54)
  - Kay Sebler thesis (Box 54)
  - Royalties, corresondence, newsletter (Box 54)
  - Carol P. Christ (Box 55)
  - Finnevara and Rujum El-Hiri (Box 55)
  - Matilda Joslyn Gage Foundation (Box 55)
  - Debra Schaffer Hubert (Box 55)
  - Women's reproductive rights (Box 55)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 55)
  - Putnam (Box 55)
  - Jane Caputi (Box 55)
  - Freida Jacques
  - Gail Bryan (Box 55)
  - "Helene Grimoud"-Ellen Burger, December 19, 2007 (Box 55)
  - Krystyna Colburn (Box 55)
  - Julie Enszer (Box 55)
  - Ann Marie Palmisciano (Box 55)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 55)
  - Correspondence-presentations/sermons (Box 55)
  - Anna and Francis Daly (mother and father) (Box 55)
  - Postcards, 60s era (Box 55)
  - Emails to Mary Daly-mainly concerning BC situation, 1999 (Box 56)
  - Personal correspondence and notes, BC emails (Box 56)
  - Correspondence, royalties (Box 56)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (for archives) (Box 56)
  - Wild Cat (Box 56)
  - Address books (Box 56)
  - From Janice Raymond for Mary (Box 56)
  - Mary and others-emails (Box 56)
  - Water women's journal (Box 56)
  - Friends-letters to and from Mary (Box 56)
  - Friends-Kady (Box 56)
  - Friends-Emily Culpepper (Box 56)
  - Friends-Kildare (Box 56)
  - Friends-Sally Gearhart (Box 56)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 56)
  - Index Directory of Women's Media (Box 56)
  - KPFA (Box 56)
  - Virginia McIntyre (Box 56)
  - Mary Daly notes and cards (Box 57)
  - Mary Daly fan club, 2013 (Box 57)
  - Lauren Bristol (Box 57)
  - Fan mail (Box 57)
  - The Church and the Second Sex fan mail (Box 57)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 57)
  - The Church and the Second Sex correspondence (Box 57)
  - The Church and the Second Sex reviews (Box 57)
  - Mail, early 1970s (Box 57)
  - Letter and notes relating to Quintessence (Box 57)
  - Correspondence-most recent (Box 57)
  - Ongoing: short notes (Box 57)
  - Desperate women (Box 57)
  - Correspondence/fan mail answered, 1989 (Box 57)
  - Quintessence fan mail (Box 57)
  - Fan mail; letters of support (Box 57)
  - Fan mail (Box 57)
  - Fan mail, 2008 (Box 57)
  - Fan mail-old (Box 57)
  - Fan mail, 1960s-1970s (Box 57)
  - Letters from Beyond God the Father, 1979 (Box 57)
  - Beyond God the Father correspondence, post May 1975, pre 1977 (Box 57)
  - Speaking engagements, personal correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 57)
  - Correspondence from women, 1986 (Box 57)
  - Beyond God the Father correspondence, 1984 (Box 57)
  - Miscellaneous fan mail, personal papers, 1997 (Box 57)
  - Letters, 1999 (Box 57)
  - Fan mail re: BC case, 1999-2000 (Box 57)
  - Mary Daly notes and cards (Box 57)
  - Fan mail, 1960s and 1970s (Box 57)
  - Fan mail, May 2000 (Box 58)
  - Fan mail (Box 58)
  - Fan mail, 1989-1991 (Box 58)
  - Pure Lust correspondence (Box 58)
  - Correspondence from women, 1985 (Box 58)
  - Correspondence Beyond God the Father (Box 58)
  - Correspondence Wickedary et al., 1988-1990 (Box 58)
  - Fan mail, Summer and fall 1987, winter 1988 (Box 58)
  - Gyn/Ecology and PureLust fan mail etc., 1993 (Box 58)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 58)
  - General correspondence answered, 1992-11-1993 (Box 58)
  - Outercourse and other correspondence, 1993 (Box 58)
  - Outercourse and other correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 58)
  - Correspondence answered, Fall 1994 (Box 58)
  - Gyn/Ecology correspondence, 1984 (Box 58)
  - Pure Lust, 1986-1987 (Box 58)
  - Gyn/Ecology letters not used in Chapter 12 (Box 58)
  - Gyn/Ecology answered, 1979 (Box 58)
  - Gyn/Ecology letters used in Chapter 12 (Box 58)
  - Answered corresondence, 1990 (Box 58)
  - Pure Lust (Box 58)
  - Fan mail (Box 58)
  - Fan mail answered, 1975 (Box 58)
  - Correspondence within books (Box 58)
  - Notes from Scapegoat (Box 58)
  - Floppy disk of correspondence, speaking engagement, and teaching folders, 1 items (1 floppy disk) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Penny Sisto Fiber Artist, 1998 (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of "Species Survival in Nuclear World" - Rosalie Bertel, Barbara Zanot, 1980-04-21; 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of "Nuclear Madness" - Dr. Helen Caldicott, 1978; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of N. Hunter followed by C. McKinnon rebuttal - WBAI radio, 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Sue Lukagorp's reading of Mary, 1986-04-14; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Terry Gross - Shere Hite - Joyce Carol Oates, 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of spoken letter from Toni, 1988-02-28; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording - to Mary Daly from Gail Murray, 1986-03-26; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording - Rosalie Bertell talk at AMARC 2, 1986-07-28; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Gladys Custance, 1974-1976; 2 items (2 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Morning Edition - WBUR - Brady, 1999-06-29; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Norma Ramos from McCarthy, 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of spoken letter from Diane Navicky (from Tacoma, WA) to Mary Daly (Box 74)
- SERIES IV. Personal, 1950-2010; 10.626 linear feet (14 containers)
  This series contains personal records of Daly, including financial reports, insurance, vet and house bills, school and university papers, family and genealogy research, photographs, and miscellaneous newspaper clippings. Personal correspondence to friends and family can be found in the correspondence series. More newspaper clippings can be found in the writings and correspondence series.
  - Auto Repairs Wellesly Volkswagen, 1999 (Box 59)
  - Will, 2006-2010 (Box 59)
  - List of Books from Mary Daly's Personal Library (Box 59)
  - Jury Duty, 1985-1987 (Box 59)
  - Investments (Box 59)
  - Jury Duty, 1993 (Box 59)
  - Automobile Repair, 1984-1987 (Box 59)
  - Shaklee, 1986-1987 (Box 59)
  - Cat Vet (Box 59)
  - Lunar Calendar, 1984 (Box 59)
  - Portugal (Box 59)
  - MacArthur Awards, 1985 (Box 59)
  - Taxes- Expenses, 1985 (Box 59)
  - Bay Bank X-press Checks, 1993 (Box 59)
  - Telephone- Newton, 1985 (Box 59)
  - Travel Expenses, 1985-1986 (Box 59)
  - Watches, 1986 (Box 59)
  - Expenses, 1985-1986 (Box 59)
  - Woman of Power, 1987 (Box 59)
  - X-Rays, 1987 (Box 59)
  - General Electric (Box 59)
  - Taxes, 1980-2001 (Box 59)
  - Now Account Bank Statements, 1986-1991 (Box 59)
  - Munen Market Statements, 1984-1996 (Box 59)
  - Nixon Arbella Insurance, 2000-2002 (Box 59)
  - Automobiles, 1987-2001 (Box 59)
  - Deposit Summaries, 1984-1986 (Box 59)
  - Bay Bank Statements, 1983-1998 (Box 59)
  - Hedd Investigation (Box 59)
  - Banking Information, 1984-1993 (Box 59)
  - Miscellaneous Personal Business Documents, 2007 (Box 59)
  - TIAA CREF, 1999 (Box 59)
  - TIAA CREF Retirement Funds, 1999-2000 (Box 59)
  - Animal/Environmental Charity Solicitations, 2001 (Box 60)
  - Research Articles, 1996 (Box 60)
  - Delray Medical Center, 2000 (Box 60)
  - Cable, 2000 (Box 60)
  - Personal Bills, 2000-2001 (Box 60)
  - Linda McCord Report, 1999 (Box 60)
  - Loose Documents, 1998 (Box 60)
  - Environment Theocracy Now, 2005 (Box 60)
  - "Stingy", 2004 (Box 60)
  - Income Tax, 2001 (Box 60)
  - Terence German Manuscript (Box 60)
  - Bush Evang., 2004 (Box 60)
  - Bush Inauguration Speech, 2001 (Box 60)
  - Coastal Erosion and Pollution, 2005 (Box 60)
  - Pollowy Tall- My Website, 2001 (Box 60)
  - Skull and Bones, 2001 (Box 60)
  - Earth Save Boston, 2001 (Box 60)
  - Pollowy Tall Anne Marie, 1997 (Box 60)
  - Lectures, 2002 (Box 60)
  - Election Thoughts Sally Raesch Wagner, 2004-2005 (Box 60)
  - Computer Instructions, 2005 (Box 60)
  - Tsunami- Global Warming and Nuclear Testing and Animals, 2005 (Box 60)
  - Torture, 2004-2005 (Box 60)
  - Truth Out Bush, 2004 (Box 60)
  - Extremely Important, 2005 (Box 60)
  - Vote Count Ohio, 2004 (Box 60)
  - Bush Administration, 2005 (Box 60)
  - Trafficking- Women and Children, 2001-2004 (Box 60)
  - Election, 2004 (Box 60)
  - Global Dimming, 2005 (Box 60)
  - Medicare Medex Summary Notice, 2002-2003 (Box 60)
  - Frauenoffensive, 2001 (Box 60)
  - Social Security Payments, 1998 (Box 60)
  - Social Security Payments, 2000 (Box 60)
  - Social Security (Personal), 2001 (Box 60)
  - Social Security Statement, 1989 (Box 60)
  - My Papers- NG Oregon Chris Kramarae, 2005 (Box 60)
  - Health, 2005-2007 (Box 60)
  - Loose Papers, 1999-2009 (Box 60)
  - Automobile Insurance, 1987-2002 (Box 60)
  - Unidentified Picture, 2001 (Box 60)
  - Educational Transcripts, 1950-1952 (Box 60)
  - Juvenalia, 1996 (Box 60)
  - X-Ray, 1993 (Box 60)
  - Obituary, 2010 (Box 60)
  - Ongoing- Personal, 1984-1986 (Box 60)
  - Homeopathy (Box 60)
  - Courses Fribourg- Georgetown Ethics/Philosophy and Class List, 1966 (Box 60)
  - Fribourg Courses History of Modern Philosophy (Box 60)
  - Dan Rather, 2003 (Box 60)
  - Fribourg Courses- Georgetown Philosophical Psychology (Box 60)
  - Fribourg Courses- Ancient and Medieval Philosophy (Box 60)
  - Bion Aire Ionization, 1978 (Box 60)
  - Brown University, 1978-1979 (Box 60)
  - Gail Bryan (Box 60)
  - Charge Accounts Statements, 1975-1979 (Box 60)
  - Chain Letter, 1976 (Box 60)
  - Blue Cross, 1986 (Box 60)
  - Social Security, 1995-1997 (Box 60)
  - Irish Genealogy and Citizenship, 1991 (Box 60)
  - Chemical Lawn, 1984-1991 (Box 60)
  - Eco Feminist Visions Emerging, 1991-1992 (Box 60)
  - FDA, 1992 (Box 60)
  - Apartment Furnishings, 1984 (Box 60)
  - Data on Bush, 2003 (Box 60)
  - DU, 2004 (Box 60)
  - Articles, 1992-1993 (Box 60)
  - Credit Information, 1992 (Box 60)
  - Repro-Technologies and Surrogacy, 1988 (Box 60)
  - Feminism: A Deeper Look, 1979 (Box 60)
  - IRS Lost Check Return, 1997 (Box 60)
  - Loose in Box, 1999 (Box 60)
  - Bosnia Rape Camps, 1992-1993 (Box 61)
  - Articles and Personal, 1998 (Box 61)
  - Loose in Box (Box 61)
  - Lioness Boob Store Sacrements (Box 61)
  - Paper Loose in Box, 1971-1991 (Box 61)